Marcello Deidda

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CONTACTS

Phone: +447490216091

Email: info@marcellodeidda.com

Based in London

PERSONAL PROFILES

LinkedIn

GitHub

CodePen

TECHNICAL SKILLS

MERN: MongoDB, Express, React, Node Python: Algorithms, Data Structs, OOP

Front-end: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

JavaScript ES6

Databases: SQLite, PostgreSQL

CERTIFICATES

Front End Development Libraries

April 2023 - freeCodeCamp

Introduction to Computer Science

December 2022 - Harvard CS50

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2022

December 2022 – Udemy

Javascript Algorithms and Data Structs

December 2021 – freeCodeCamp

Responsive Web Design

November 2021 - freeCodeCamp

LANGUAGES

Italian - Native Speaker

English – Full proficiency

French – Full proficiency

Japanese - Limited Proficiency

Highly skilled Fullstack Developer specialising in the MERN stack with a recent completion of a Software Engineering Bootcamp funded by the DfE. Self-motivated and passionate about continuous learning, with a strong focus on personal development. Experienced teacher and excellent communicator.

PORTFOLIO

Full Stack - Node.js / Express / MongoDB:

BookApp // [Github] (IN PROGRESS)

Front End – HTML / CSS / Javascript / React.js:

- Work Session Pacer // [Github]
- Rating Stars // [Github]
- Finance Calculators Web // [Github]

Software Development – Python / SQLite:

Ebookstore database // [Github]

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineering Bootcamp

University of Manchester & HyperionDev

November 2022 - February 2023

- Completed with 100% marks, ranking 2nd out of 300 students
- Developed proficiency in Python, OOP, HTML, CSS, SQLite

Self-employed violinist and music teacher

September 2015 – Current

- Performances in chamber music and orchestral settings
- Teaching violin, piano and music theory to students of 4 to 80yo
- Preparation for graded music exams with a 100% success rate

Restaurant Crew

Woko Vaise - Lyon (France)

September 2014 – August 2014

- Handle customer orders, provide table service, maintain restaurant operations

EDUCATION

Master's Degree, Advanced Instrument Studies

Guildhall School of Music & Drama, UK 2015 – 2016

Diplome d'Etudes Musicales

Conservatoire de Lyon, France 2011 – 2015

Diploma di Violino (Bachelor degree equivalent)

Conservatorio di Musica di Cagliari, Italy 2011

Diploma di Liceo Scientifico (A-level equivalent)

Liceo scientifico statale "A. Pacinotti", Italy 2010

Maths, Physics, Chemistry, Biology, Literature, History, Philosophy, English, Latin, Arts